Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 1989.0080
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series IV: Administrative Records, undated, 1925-1991
  - Subseries E: Conventions, 1958-1990
    - 1988 (Box 194)
      - Verbatim proceedings (Box 195)
    - 1989 Convention (Box 195)
      - Affiliates list (Box 195)
      - Arrangements committee (Box 195)
      - Assorted news clippings (Box 195)
      - CLC Vice President (Box 195)
      - Community Service Committee (Box 195)
      - Constitutional Amendments (Box 195)
      - Constitutional Committee (Box 195)
      - Convention greetings (Box 195)
      - Credentials committee (Box 195)
      - Education Committee (Box 195)
      - Executive Board Nominees and Candidates (Box 195)
      - Legislative Committee (Box 195)
      - Materials for printers (Box 195)
      - Materials ordered for kits (Box 195)
      - Miscellaneous papers (Box 195)
      - Officers' and Committee reports (Box 195)
      - Per capita strength (Box 195)
      - Presidential campaign (Box 195)
      - Reports (Box 195)
      - Resolutions, (2 fl) (Box 195)
      - Resolutions committee (Box 195)
      - Rules Committee (Box 195)
      - Speakers and invitations (Box 195)
      - Suites (Box 195)
      - Union display tables (Box 195)
      - Women's CommitteeBoard (Box 195)
      - Verbatim proceedings, (3 fl) (Box 195)
    - 1990 Convention
      - Arrangements Committee (Box 198)
      - C.O.P.E. recommendations for federal candidates (Box 198)
      - C.O.P.E. recommendations for state candidates (Box 198)
      - Community Services Committee (Box 198)
      - Constitution Committee (Box 198)
      - Credentials Committee (Box 198)
      - District caucuses (Box 198)
      - Education Committee (Box 198)
      - Escort Committees (Box 198)
      - Executive Board and principle officers of affiliates (Box 198)
      - Legislative Committee (Box 198)
      - Material for printer (Box 198)
      - Materials ordered for kits (Box 198)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 198)
      - Officers and committee reports (Box 198)
      - Per capita strength (Box 198)
      - Reports (Box 198)
      - Resolutions (Box 198)
      - Resolutions Committee (Box 198)
      - Resolutions submitted to the 34th Annual Convention of the Connecticut State AFL-CIO, 1990 (Box 198)
      - Rules Committee (Box 198)
      - Speakers and invitations (Box 198)
      - Women and Civil Rights Breakfast (Box 198)
  - Subseries F: Committees, undated, 1952-1991
    - Atomic Energy Committee, 1957-1962 (Box 32:, Folder 1379-1382)
    - Betty Tianti Scholarship Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Citizens Anti-Communist Committee of CT, undated (Box 32:, Folder 1383)
    - Civil Rights Committee, 1958 (Box 32:, Folder 1384-1387)
    - Civil Rights, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3534)
    - CLC Presidents Committee, undated (Box 193)
    - C.L.C. Presidents Committee, undated (Box 198)
    - Community Services Committee, 1960-1978 (Box 32:, Folder 1388-1391)
    - Community Services, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3533)
    - Community Services Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Community Services Committee, undated (Box 193)
    - Community Services Committee, undated (Box 203)
    - Connecticut
      - Humanities Council, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3531)
      - Joint Council on Economic Education, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3532)
    - Constitution Committee, 1959 (Box 33:, Folder 1392)
    - COPE Retiree Committee, undated (Box 193)
    - Correspondence Committee, 1961 (Box 33:, Folder 1393)
    - DRG Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Economic Freedom, undated (Box 33:, Folder 1394)
    - Education, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3535)
    - Education Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 33:, Folder 1396)
    - Education Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Finance Committee, Connecticut General Assembly, 1961 (Box 33:, Folder 1397)
    - Governor's Committee on the employment of the handicapped, undated (Box 193)
    - Health and Safety Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Health and Safety Committee, undated (Box 193)
    - Health and Safety Committee, undated (Box 198)
    - Health and Safety Committee, undated (Box 203)
    - Health Care Committee, undated (Box 203)
    - Health Care Cost Containment Committee, undated (Box 193)
    - Homefront Lobbying, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3536)
    - Jewish Committees, undated (Box 193)
    - Jewish labor, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3537)
    - Labor Committee transcripts, 1952-1966 (Box 33:, Folder 1398-1402)
    - Legislative, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3538)
    - Legislative Committee (state), undated (Box 198)
    - Legislative Action, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3539)
    - Lobbyist Committee, undated (Box 193)
    - Lobbyist Committee, undated (Box 198)
    - Nautilus, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3540)
    - Organizing, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3541)
    - Organizing Committee, undated (Box 194)
    - OSHA, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3542)
    - Plant Closing Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Prevailing Rates of Wages, 1959-1960 (Box 33:, Folder 1403)
    - Public Employees, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3543)
    - Public Employee Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Regional Plan Association, 1958 (Box 33:, Folder 1395)
    - Report of the Resolutions Committee, undated (Box 195)
    - Standing committees, 1988 (Box 191)
    - State Federation Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 203)
    - State Legislative Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - State Occupational Informational Coordinating, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3544)
    - Steering Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 33:, Folder 1404)
    - Strike Assistance, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3545)
    - Strike Assistance Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Strike Assistance Committee, undated (Box 198)
    - Union Label Committee, 1957-1961 (Box 33:, Folder 1405-1406)
    - Women and Civil Rights Committee, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Women and Civil Rights Committee, undated (Box 194)
    - Women's and Civil Rights Committee, undated (Box 203)
    - Women's Rights Committee, undated (Box 33:, Folder 1407)
    - Worker's Compensation Advisory Committee, undated (Box 203)
  - Subseries G: Commissions, undated, 1955-1980
    - Civil Rights Commission, CT, 1958-1963 (Box 33:, Folder 1408-1409)
    - Civil Rights Commission, Federal, 1960 (Box 33:, Folder 1410)
    - Compensation, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3547)
    - Employment of Handicapped, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3548)
    - High Technology, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3550)
    - Hospital and health care, Commission on, undated (Box 193)
    - Hospitals and Health Care, Commission on, undated (Box 198)
    - Hospital and Health Care Commission, undated (Box 203)
    - John Arcudi, CT workers, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3546)
    - Judicial Selection Commission, undated (Box 193)
    - Management of State Government, Commission to Study, undated (Box 203)
    - The New Haven Commission, 1955 (Box 33:, Folder 1411)
    - New England Regional Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 33:, Folder 1412)
    - Permanent Commission on the Status of Women, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3551)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1959-1962 (Box 33:, Folder 1414)
    - River Basin Commission, 1958-1980 (Box 33:, Folder 1413)
    - State Ethics, undated (Box 122:, Folder 3549)
    - Study Welfare Laws, 1960-1962 (Box 33:, Folder 1415-1417)
    - Workmen's Compensation Commission, 1961 (Box 33:, Folder 1418)
  - Subseries H: Conferences, 1925-1981
    - AFL-CIO Regional conference, 1981 (Box 33:, Folder 1419)
    - AFL-CIO Atomic Radiation Hazards, 1957 (Box 33:, Folder 1420)
    - Automation, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3580)
    - Conference on Automation, 1964 (Box 34:, Folder 1421)
    - Children and Youth, White House Conference, 1958-1960 (Box 34:, Folder 1422)
    - Community Services Conference, 1925-1927 (Box 34:, Folder 1423-1426)
    - Community Services Institute, 1979 (Box 34:, Folder 1427)
    - Employment Conference, 1926 (Box 34:, Folder 1428)
    - Employment: Problems of Working Women, 1967 (Box 34:, Folder 1429)
    - Farm Workers Luncheon, 1974 (Box 34:, Folder 1430)
    - Conference on Human Rights, 1964 (Box 34:, Folder 1431-1432)
    - CT Society of Gerontology, 1960 (Box 34:, Folder 1433)
    - Conference on Human Rights, 1964 (Box 34:, Folder 1434)
    - Industrial Relations Research Association meeting, 1972 (Box 34:, Folder 1435)
    - Industrial Union Department meeting, 1961 (Box 34:, Folder 1436)
    - International Trade, 1962 (Box 34:, Folder 1437-1440)
    - Labor and Community Services, 1974 (Box 34:, Folder 1441)
    - Labor Management, 1959 (Box 34:, Folder 1442)
    - Labor Movement, 1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1443)
    - Legislative, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3576)
    - New England Conference, 1958-1962 (Box 34:, Folder 1444)
    - Economic Future of New England Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1445)
    - Economic Opportunity, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3583)
    - Educational, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3577)
    - Health Care, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3584)
    - International Trade, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3579)
    - OSHA Conference, 1977 (Box 34:, Folder 1446-1448)
    - Public Employees Conference, 1958-1959 (Box 34:, Folder 1449)
    - Conference of Social Work (CT), 1960-1962 (Box 34:, Folder 1450-1451)
    - Unemployment Conference, 1959 (Box 34:, Folder 1452)
    - Union Label, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3581)
    - Union Label, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3585)
    - Union Label, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3586)
    - U.S. Security of the Soviet Challenge Conference, 1979 (Box 34:, Folder 1453)
    - War on Poverty, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3582)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1960 (Box 34:, Folder 1454)
    - Women's, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3578)
    - Women's Conference on Consumer Problems, 1961 (Box 34:, Folder 1455)
    - Women in Unions Conference, 1959 (Box 34:, Folder 1456)
    - Workmen's Compensation Conference, 1960 (Box 34:, Folder 1457)
  - Subseries I: Affiliated Unions, undated, 1951-1988
    - Actors Equity, 1987 (Box 191)
    - AFSCME, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3588)
    - Airline pilots, 1962 (Box 35:, Folder 1458)
    - Airline Pilots Association, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3590)
    - All Affiliates, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3587)
    - Allied industrial workers, 1962 (Box 35:, Folder 1459)
    - Allied Industrial Workers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3591)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union, 1962-1964 (Box 35:, Folder 1460)
    - American Federation of Government Employees, undated (Box 198)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, No. 4, undated (Box 202)
    - Asbestos Workers, 1962 (Box 35:, Folder 1461)
    - Asbestos workers, undated (Box 193)
    - ATEP, undated (Box 124:, Folder 3589)
    - Automobile, aerospace, agricultural workers, 1962-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1462)
    - Bakers union, 1960 (Box 35:, Folder 1465)
    - Bakery, Confectionary and Tobacco, undated (Box 202)
    - Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3592)
    - Barbers, hairdressers, cosmetologists, proprietors, 1962-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1463)
    - Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmetologists and Proprietors, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3593)
    - Boilermakers, ironship builders, blacksmiths, forgers, undated (Box 35:, Folder 1464)
    - Boilermakers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3594)
    - Boilermakers, undated (Box 193)
    - Brewery, flour, cereal, soft drink, distillery workers, 1962-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1466)
    - Brick and clay workers, 1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1467)
    - Bricklayers, 1978 (Box 180)
    - Bricklayers, masons, plasterers, 1962-1971 (Box 35:, Folder 1468)
    - Bridgeport Brass, undated (Box 143)
    - Broadcast employees, undated (Box 198)
    - Broadcast employees and technicians, 1962 (Box 35:, Folder 1469)
    - Building and Construction Trades Amalgamated, CT clothing and textile workers, undated (Box 181)
    - Building and Construction Trades Council, 1986 (Box 180)
    - Building and Construction Trades, 1987 (Box 191)
    - Building and construction trades, undated (Box 198)
    - Building service employees, 1958-1965 (Box 35:, Folder 1470)
    - Building and construction trades, undated (Box 193)
    - Building and construction trades, undated (Box 202)
    - C. Bronze, undated (Box 143)
    - Carpenters, United Brotherhood of, 1985 (Box 180)
    - Carpenters and joiners, 1965-1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1471)
    - Carpenters and Joiners, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3595)
    - Central Labor Councils, undated (Box 181)
    - Central Labor Councils, undated (Box 198)
    - Carpenters, 1987 (Box 191)
    - Carpenters, undated (Box 193)
    - Carpenters, undated (Box 198)
    - Carpenters, undated (Box 202)
    - Chemical workers, undated (Box 35:, Folder 1472)
    - Chemical workers, 1979-1985 (Box 180)
    - Chemical workers, undated (Box 198)
    - Chemical workers, undated (Box 202)
    - Chemical, oil and atomic workers, 1953 (Box 35:, Folder 1473)
    - Cleaners and dryers, 1960 (Box 35:, Folder 1474)
    - Clothing workers, 1962-1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1475)
    - Clothing workers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3596)
    - Clothing and textile workers, 1987 (Box 180)
    - Clothing and textile workers ( ACTWU), undated (Box 193)
    - Clothing and Textile Workers ( ACTWU), undated (Box 198)
    - Communications workers, 1962-1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1476)
    - Communications workers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3597)
    - Communications workers, undated (Box 193)
    - Communication workers, undated (Box 198)
    - Communications Workers of America, undated (Box 181)
    - CT State Employees Association, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3598)
    - Dictaphone, undated (Box 143)
    - Directly affiliated unions, 1962-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1477)
    - Distillery, rectifying wine and allied workers, 1965-1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1478)
    - Distillery, Rectifying Wine and Allied workers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3599)
    - Drug and Hospital workers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3600-3601)
    - E.B. Guards, undated; (2 fl.) (Box 143)
    - Electrical radio and machine workers, 1962-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1480)
    - Electrical, Radio and Machine workers ( IUE), undated (Box 125:, Folder 3602)
    - I.U.E., 1988 (Box 191)
    - International Union of Electricians, undated (Box 198)
    - Electrical workers, 1962-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1479)
    - Electrical workers ( IBEW), undated (Box 125:, Folder 3603)
    - Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood, undated (Box 181)
    - Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood of ( IBEW), undated (Box 193)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, undated (Box 198)
    - I.B.E.W., undated (Box 202)
    - Elevator constructors, 1967 (Box 35:, Folder 1482)
    - Engineers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3604)
    - Engineers ( IUE), undated (Box 193)
    - Engineers (Operating), 1988 (Box 191)
    - Engineers operating international, 1971-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1483)
    - Engineers, Operating ( IUOE), undated (Box 193)
    - International Union of Operating Engineers ( I.U.O.E.), undated (Box 202)
    - Engineers technical, 1965 (Box 35:, Folder 1484)
    - Farm workers, 1968-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1485)
    - Farm Workers, United, undated (Box 181)
    - Fenner Company, undated (Box 143)
    - Fire fighters, 1963-1972 (Box 35:, Folder 1486)
    - Firefighters, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3605)
    - Fire Fighters, undated (Box 181)
    - Firefighters, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Fire fighters, undated (Box 193)
    - Fitzgerald Company, undated (Box 143)
    - Food and commercial workers, 1986 (Box 180)
    - Food and Commercial Workers (United), 1988 (Box 191)
    - Food and Commercial Workers, United, undated (Box 181)
    - Food handlers, 1962-1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1487)
    - Food handlers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3606-3607)
    - Furniture workers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3608)
    - Garment workers, 1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1488)
    - Garment workers ( ILUGW), undated (Box 125:, Folder 3609)
    - Garment Workers Union, International Ladies', undated (Box 181)
    - Garment Workers, International Ladies, undated (Box 198)
    - Garment Workers, International Ladies ( ILGWU), undated (Box 193)
    - Glass bottle blowers, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3610)
    - Glass Workers, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Glass workers, undated (Box 202)
    - Government employees, 1964 (Box 35:, Folder 1489)
    - Government employees, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3611)
    - Government Employees, American Federation of, undated (Box 181)
    - Graphic arts, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3612)
    - Graphic Communications, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Graphic Communications International, 1986 (Box 180)
    - Hatters, cap and millinary workers, undated (Box 35:, Folder 1490)
    - Health Care Employees, 1199, undated (Box 181)
    - Health Care Employees, 1199, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Hotel employees, undated (Box 125:, Folder 3613)
    - Hotel Employees (HERE), undated (Box 193)
    - Hotel employees, Restaurant Employees, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Hotel and Restaurant, undated (Box 198)
    - Hotel and restaurant employees, undated (Box 202)
    - Hotel employees, restaurant employees, undated (Box 181)
    - Hotel, restaurant employees and bartenders, 1963-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1491)
    - Insurance workers, 1962-1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1492)
    - Insurance workers international, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3614)
    - Iron workers, undated (Box 35:, Folder 1493)
    - Ironworkers, undated (Box 181)
    - Ironworkers, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Ironworkers, undated (Box 193)
    - Ironworkers, undated (Box 202)
    - Iron workers International, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3615)
    - Jewelry workers, 1961-1963 (Box 35:, Folder 1494-1495)
    - Laborers, 1971-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1496)
    - Laborers, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3616)
    - Laborers, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Laborers, undated (Box 193)
    - Letter carriers, 1962 (Box 35:, Folder 1497)
    - Letter carriers, undated (Box 193)
    - Letter Carriers, National Association of, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3617)
    - Letter Carriers, National Association of, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Lithographers, 1964 (Box 35:, Folder 1498)
    - Longshoremen International, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3618)
    - Longshoremen's Union, International, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Machine workers, 1962-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1481)
    - Machinists, 1962-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1499)
    - Machinists, undated (Box 181)
    - Machinists, undated (Box 193)
    - Machinists, undated (Box 198)
    - Machinists, undated (Box 202)
    - Machinists and aerospace, 1986 (Box 180)
    - Mail to all affiliates, undated (Box 193)
    - Marine Engineers Association, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3619)
    - Metal Trades Council, 1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1500)
    - Metal Trades Council, undated (Box 198)
    - Metal Trades Council, undated (Box 202)
    - Metal Trades Council of New London County, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3620)
    - Mine workers, 1961 (Box 35:, Folder 1501)
    - Musicians, undated (Box 181)
    - Musicians, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Musicians, undated (Box 193)
    - Musicians, undated (Box 202)
    - Musicians, American Federation, 1968-1973 (Box 35:, Folder 1502)
    - Musicians, American Federation of, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3621)
    - New England Health Care employees, undated (Box 194)
    - Newspaper Guild, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3622)
    - Newspaper Guild, undated (Box 198)
    - Newspaper Guild, 240 (Bristol), 1988 (Box 191)
    - Northeast AFL-CIO Council, undated (Box 181)
    - Northeast AFL-CIO Council, undated (Box 198)
    - Not affiliated, undated (Box 198)
    - Office and Professional Employees International Union, 1985 (Box 180)
    - OPEIU, 1988 (Box 191)
    - OPEIU, undated (Box 194)
    - O.P.E.I.U., undated (Box 198)
    - Office and professional employees, local 376, undated (Box 181)
    - Office employees, 1959-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1503)
    - Office Employees, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3623)
    - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, undated (Box 198)
    - Other state federations, undated (Box 181)
    - Other state federations, undated (Box 198)
    - Other state federations, undated (Box 202)
    - Painters, decorators, paperhangers, 1963-1973 (Box 35:, Folder 1504)
    - Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3624)
    - Papermakers and workers, 1964-1968 (Box 35:, Folder 1505)
    - Papermakers and Workers, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3625)
    - Paperworkers, undated (Box 181)
    - Paperworkers, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Paperworkers, undated (Box 198)
    - Paperworkers, undated (Box 202)
    - PATCO, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3626)
    - Plumber, undated
      - 133, undated (Box 181)
      - 133 constitutions, due books, undated (Box 181)
    - Plumbers, undated (Box 194)
    - Plumbers, undated (Box 198)
    - Plumbing and pipefitting, journeymen and apprentices, 1963-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1506)
    - Plumbing and Pipefitting, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3627)
    - Police ( AFSCME Council 15), undated (Box 181)
    - Police ( AFSCME Council 15), undated (Box 198)
    - Police Association (AFSCME 15), undated (Box 194)
    - Post office motor vehicle employees, 1963-1966 (Box 35:, Folder 1507)
    - Postal clerks, 1964-1967 (Box 35:, Folder 1508)
    - Postal clerks, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3628-3629)
    - Postal workers, 1986 (Box 180)
    - Postal Workers, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Postal workers, undated (Box 194)
    - Postal workers, undated (Box 202)
    - Preferred Utilities, undated (Box 143)
    - Printing pressmen and assistants, 1964-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1509)
    - Protective Services, undated (Box 181)
    - Pulp, sulphite and papermill workers, 1967 (Box 35:, Folder 1510)
    - Public employees, 1967-1973 (Box 35:, Folder 1511)
    - Radio and television stations, undated (Box 194)
    - Railroad workers, undated (Box 198)
    - Railway, airline clerks, undated (Box 181)
    - Railway and airline clerks, 1981-1985 (Box 180)
    - Railway Carmen, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3630)
    - Reports, 1962-1984 (Box 128:, Folder 3655-3664)
    - Retail clerks, 1962-1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1512)
    - Retail Clerks Association, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3631)
    - Retail, Wholesale department, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3632)
    - Roofers, 1963 (Box 35:, Folder 1513)
    - Roofers, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3633)
    - Roofers, 1986 (Box 180)
    - Rubber, cork, linoleum and plastic workers, 1965, 1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1514)
    - Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic workers, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3634)
    - SASCO, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3635)
    - School administrators, 1984 (Box 180)
    - School Administrators, undated (Box 181)
    - Seafarers International Union, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3636)
    - Service employees, 1951 (Box 35:, Folder 1515)
    - Service employees, undated (Box 181)
    - Service Employees, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Service employees, undated (Box 198)
    - Service Employees International, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3637)
    - Service Employees International, 1985 (Box 180)
    - Service Employees International Union, undated (Box 194)
    - 1199/ SEIU, undated (Box 198)
    - Sheet metal workers, 1965-1966 (Box 35:, Folder 1516)
    - Sheet Metal workers, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3638)
    - Sheet Metal Workers, 1988 (Box 191)
    - State, county, and municipal employees (AFSCME), undated (Box 194)
    - Steel workers, undated (Box 35:, Folder 1517)
    - Steel workers, undated (Box 126:, Folder 3639-3640)
    - Steelworkers, 1986 (Box 180)
    - Steelworkers, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Steelworkers, undated (Box 194)
    - Steelworkers, undated (Box 198)
    - Steelworkers, undated (Box 202)
    - Stenotypers, 1963 (Box 35:, Folder 1518)
    - Teachers, undated (Box 194)
    - Teachers, undated (Box 127:, Folder 3641-3644)
    - Teachers, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Teachers, undated (Box 198)
    - Teachers, undated (Box 202)